http://www.stata.com/privacy-policy/

Stata/MP4 Annual License (download)
Stata
Why Stata?
Features
New in Stata 16
Disciplines
Stata/MP
Which Stata is right for me?
SUPPORT
Ready. Set. Go Stata.
Last updated: 16 January 2020
StataCorp LLC (StataCorp) strives to provide our users with exceptional
products and services. To do so, we must collect personal information
from you. This information is necessary to conduct business with our
existing and potential customers. We collect and use this information
only where we may legally do so. This policy explains what personal
information we collect, how we use it, and what rights you have to that
information.
What personal information does StataCorp collect?
Depending on the circumstances, the following are the types of personal information you might provide us:
Name
Email address
Delivery, billing, and mailing addresses
Phone number(s)
Company/institution name
Company tax ID number
Proof of academic affiliation as necessary to provide applicable pricing
Payment information
Product information and technical support requests
Stata license information
Device and network information, such as your IP address and operating system
Why does StataCorp collect personal information about you?
To buy from us, you must provide contact information, such as your name and delivery address, and financial information, such as your credit card number and expiration date. This information is used for billing purposes and to process your order. In addition, if we have questions concerning an order, we will use this information to contact you. For orders placed on our
website, our method for contacting you will be email. The following are reasons we need your personal information:
To process and deliver orders that you place with us or that are placed on your behalf, and to provide you with documentation or other material in support of such orders
To provide products, services, and support requested by you or on your behalf
To provide responsive and accurate information in conjunction with an order for products or services
To manage licenses or subscriptions for the use of our products and services
To obtain feedback measuring your satisfaction with Stata products and services
To provide information regarding the renewal or expiration of agreements, version upgrades, and other notifications about Stata and services that you license or use
To administer and improve our products, websites, and services
To send the Stata News, which is a free publication containing announcements of new releases and updates, articles discussing Stata's features, meetings, new products, and other announcements of interest to Stata users; you may opt out
To fulfill our contractual agreements or comply with obligations imposed by applicable laws
How does StataCorp collect personal information?
When you create an account on our website
When you request information for products and services
When you use chat
When you place an order for products or services
When you download software from our servers
When you register your Stata license
When you sign up for our newsletter, product and training alerts, or trainings/webinars
When you enter prize drawings or have your conference badge scanned at conferences
When you fill out surveys at training courses or seminars hosted by StataCorp
When you do any of the above through one of our dealers
When does StataCorp share your personal information?
We share customer information with our authorized international dealers
who have a legitimate interest to receive such information to be able to
provide local support and services to international customers. Dealers
comply with the privacy laws set forth in their respective countries.
We do not sell or give customer information to any third party (except to our authorized international dealers and payment processors).
We enter the information you give us into a customer database system that only StataCorp employees can access.
How long does StataCorp store your personal information?
We may keep your personal information to allow us to manage our relationship with you and to provide you with relevant product and service information, but we will keep it no longer than is necessary.
How can you access or correct the personal information StataCorp stores about you?
You can update your profile by logging on and following the prompts, if you have created an online account.
You may request to obtain the personal information we maintain on you by emailing service@stata.com.
You may request that StataCorp update, correct, or remove your personal information by emailing service@stata.com. Removal of some personal information may prevent use of certain products and services. StataCorp may decline to delete certain personal information if required by state or federal law.
How does StataCorp protect your personal information?
StataCorp is committed to protecting the privacy of the personal information collected.
We take precautions to protect your information. When you submit sensitive information via the website, your information is protected both online and offline.
Wherever we collect sensitive information (such as credit card data), that information is encrypted and transmitted to us in a secure way. You can verify this by looking for a lock icon in the address bar and looking for "https" at the beginning of the address of the webpage.
While we use encryption to protect sensitive information transmitted online, we also protect your information offline. The computers/servers in which we store personally identifiable information are kept in a secure environment.
StataCorp takes reasonable steps to make sure your personal information is accurate, complete, current, and otherwise reliable with regard to its intended use.
StataCorp takes appropriate measures to maintain the confidentiality of, to prevent the unauthorized use or disclosure of, and to protect this information from loss and misuse. This includes maintaining a system of administrative, physical, and technical safeguards to secure such information, such as firewalls, secure (https) web forms, and access control lists.
Does StataCorp use cookies?
This website uses cookies to provide you with a better user experience. A cookie is a small piece of data our website stores on a site visitor's hard drive and accesses each time you visit so we can
improve your access to our site, better understand how you use our site, and serve you content that may be of interest to you. For instance, we store a cookie when you log in to our shopping cart so that we can maintain your shopping cart should you not complete checkout. We do not store any personally identifiable information in cookies. If you choose to disable cookies when accessing our website, certain features, such as the shopping cart, may be impacted.
Supplemental Notice to California Residents
Effective January 1, 2020
If you are a California resident, the California Consumer Privacy Act
("CCPA") requires we disclose the following information about how we
collect, use, and disclose your personal data.
For information about what categories of personal information we may
collect from our customers, the sources of that information, the purpose
for collecting and using that information, and whom we may share that
information with, please see the sections titled
What personal information does StataCorp collect?
How does StataCorp collect personal information?
Why does StataCorp collect personal information about you?
When does StataCorp share your personal information?
California residents have the following rights:
The right to request information about personal information we have
collected about you in the 12 months preceding your request (including
the categories of information collected, the sources of that
information, the business purpose of that collection, and the specific
pieces of personal information collected). We do not sell or give
customer information to any third party (except to our authorized international
dealers who have a legitimate interest to receive such
information to be able to provide local support and services to our
international customers and our payment processors).
The right to receive requested information in a readily usable format
if provided electronically.
The right to request we delete any personal information about you that
we have collected. Removal of some personal information may prevent use of certain products and services. StataCorp may decline to delete certain personal information if required by state or federal law.
The right to opt-out of the sale of personal information to third
parties. We do not sell or give customer information to any third
party (except to our authorized international dealers who have a legitimate
interest to receive such information to be able to provide local
support and services to our international customers and our payment
processors).
The right to freely exercise your rights without being denied goods or
services.
For information about how to obtain or request deletion of your personal
information, please see How can you access or correct the personal information StataCorp stores about you?
StataCorp reserves the right to change this privacy policy as may be necessary from time to time or as may be required by law. Any changes will be posted on the StataCorp website (www.stata.com/privacy-policy).
How can you contact StataCorp?
StataCorp LLC
4905 Lakeway Drive
College Station, Texas 77845-4512
USA
1-800-782-8272 (U.S.)
1-800-248-8272 (Canada)
1-979-696-4600 (worldwide)
service@stata.com
Stata
New in Stata
Why Stata?
All features
Features by disciplines
Stata/MP
Which Stata is right for me?
20% off Gift Shop purchases! Sale ends 12/11 at 11:59 PM CT. Use promo code GIFT20.
